<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<dataroot>
<standards>
<interestRate1>0.1</interestRate1>
<interestRate2>0.15</interestRate2>
<interestRate3>0.20</interestRate3>
<interestRate4>0.30</interestRate4>
<salesTax>0.09</salesTax>
</standards>
<shoes>
<ID>1</ID>
<brand>Adidas</brand>
<name>Yeezy 350 V2 Core Black Red</name>
<cost>1345.00</cost>
<size>11</size>
<pic>350V2Red.jpg</pic>
<category>Sneaker, Running, Lifestyle, Kanye West</category>
<detail>The Yeezy Boost 350 V2 maintained its grip hold on sneaker culture with a trio of releases – red, green, and copper colorways. Each pair released on November 23, 2016. Here, we highlight the clean "Red" colorway, featuring the winning combination of a black woven Primeknit upper, a TPU midsole that covers comforting Boost cushioning, and a vibrant red stripe that runs from heel to toe. The patented "SPLY-350" message appears throughout the aforementioned stripe. Speckles of red also appear throughout the upper. The result is a clean and simple rendition of the Yeezy Boost 350 V2 that can be dressed up or worn casually.</detail>
</shoes>
<shoes>
<ID>2</ID>
<brand>Nike</brand>
<name>OFF-WHITE x Air Jordan 1 'Chicago'</name>
<cost>5400.00</cost>
<size>9</size>
<pic>NikeOffWhite.jpg</pic>
<category>Virgil Abloh, Red, Heat, The 10</category>
<detail>The verdict is in: The OFF-WHITE x Air Jordan 1 by Virgil Abloh is the sneaker of the year for 2017. The shoe absolutely everybody wants but few can get, the sneaker world has not seen a force like the Virgil Abloh Air Jordan 1 from “THE TEN” collection in a long time, if ever. Based off the original “Chicago” Air Jordan 1, the shoe features details that coincide with the rest of the ten models by Abloh like exposed foam, stitched on Swooshes, and the signature red zip tie. Sure to go down as one of the most hyped and coveted sneakers of all time, grab your piece of sneaker history now before they’re all gone.</detail>
</shoes>
<shoes>
<ID>3</ID>
<brand>Nike</brand>
<name>Nike Air Max 1/97 'Sean Wotherspoon'</name>
<cost>1799.00</cost>
<size>10</size>
<pic>NikeWootherspoon.jpg</pic>
<category>Sneaker, Lifestyle, Yellow, Handcrafted</category>
<detail>Created by popular demand. Sean Wotherspoon’s winning Air Max sneaker design from the RevolutionAIR voting campaign in early 2017 is now a reality. His creation, the Air Max 1/97 VF SW, features a hybrid design of the Air Max 97 upper in a unique multi-colored corduroy build on top of the iconic tooling of the Air Max 1. Released early in November 2017, Sean actually drove around Los Angeles giving out free pairs of the coveted Air Max 1/97 before the official retail release on Air Max Day 2018.</detail>
</shoes>
<shoes>
<ID>4</ID>
<brand>Nike</brand>
<name>Nike Air Fear of God 1 'Light Bone'</name>
<cost>1035.00</cost>
<size>13</size>
<pic>NikeFOG.jpg</pic>
<category>Basketball, Jerry Lorenzo, Grey</category>
<detail>The Nike Air Fear of God 1 “Light Bone” was one of the shoes to come out of the epic collaboration between Fear of God founder Jerry Lorenzo and Nike Sportswear in late 2018. Lorenzo’s Air Fear of God 1 “Light Bone” is constructed with a premium full-grain leather upper in an off-white shade and has a distinctive high-top silhouette. The upper of the Light Bone colorway is built entirely in leather, in contrast from the leather and ballistic nylon combination found on the black colorway. Blurring the lines between street fashion and basketball performance, the Fear of God 1 features a sculpted midsole with a large visible Zoom Air unit in the heel. The Nike Air Fear of God 1 “Light Bone” released on December 15, 2018 to instantly become one of the most sought-after sneakers of the year.</detail>
</shoes>
<shoes>
<ID>5</ID>
<brand>Nike</brand>
<name>Nike Adapt BB “Basketball - Self-Lacing”</name>
<cost>540.00</cost>
<size>11</size>
<pic>NikeBB.jpg</pic>
<category>Basketball, Technology</category>
<detail>The Nike Adapt BB “Basketball - Self-Lacing” is the first power lacing basketball shoe from Nike. The innovative design further advances the motorized lacing system that Nike debuted in the HyperAdapt, and perfects it for use on the basketball court. The Adapt BB utilizes a custom motor and gear train that senses the tension needed by each foot as soon as you slip them on and adjusts the fit accordingly. The shoe allows the wearer to fine tune the fit of each foot to their own needs, and they can be tightened or loosened during the course of the game with the touch of a button on each shoe. The Adapt BB can also be connected to your smartphone and controlled remotely. For power, the Adapt BB is packaged with a wireless charging system. The auto-lacing Nike Adapt BB basketball shoe released in February 2019.</detail>
</shoes>
<shoes>
<ID>6</ID>
<brand>Adidas</brand>
<name>Adidas DAME4 Bape</name>
<cost>359.00</cost>
<size>8</size>
<pic>AdidasBape.jpg</pic>
<category>Basketball, Bape</category>
<detail>Streetwear legends BAPE teamed up with adidas Basketball for the first time in 2018, presenting the BAPE x adidas Dame 4 collection. Featuring BAPE’s signature shark and camouflage graphics, Damian Lillard’s fourth signature shoe transformed into a hypebeast’s dream, easily becoming the most wanted set of releases in the history of Lillard’s sneaker line by far. Here we have the green camo edition, featuring BAPE’s famous camouflage motif across the upper, shark tooth graphic on the midsole, and a gum rubber outsole. The green BAPE adidas Dame 4 released in extremely limited quantities and sold out instantly on February 16, 2018.</detail>
</shoes>
<shoes>
<ID>7</ID>
<brand>Gucci</brand>
<name>Gucci Ace embroidered 'Loved'</name>
<cost>670.00</cost>
<size>8</size>
<pic>Gucci.jpg</pic>
<category>Luxury, White, Sneaker</category>
<detail>The retro inspired design of the Ace sneaker is embellished with an embroidered "Loved" appliqué along the sides—an evolution of the phrase "Blind for Love" which has become synonymous with the House.</detail>
</shoes>
<shoes>
<ID>8</ID>
<brand>Balenciaga</brand>
<name>Speed Trainer</name>
<cost>780.00</cost>
<size>11</size>
<pic>Balenciaga.jpg</pic>
<category>Luxury, Training, Running, Black</category>
<detail>Balenciaga elevates the sock-like construction of performance athletic footwear in a streamlined knit high-top set on an oversized articulated sole for a sporty, forward-looking profile.</detail>
</shoes>
<shoes>
<ID>9</ID>
<brand>Christian Loubotin</brand>
<name>Roller-Boat Men's Flat</name>
<cost>1195.00</cost>
<size>10</size>
<pic>Loubotin.jpg</pic>
<category>Luxury, Formal, Black</category>
<detail>Christian Louboutin’s Roller Boat toes the line between sneaker and boat shoe. This sporty-luxe slip-on is crafted from black suede and glistens with every evenly hand-placed black signature stud. They are finished with grosgrain piping and black side elastics for easy wear.</detail>
</shoes>
</dataroot>